> > Brian Holt: 现在我想向你们展示如何做点什么，在我看来，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now I wanna show you
how to do something, in my opinion,
这里挺酷的
pretty cool here.
这有点烦琐
This is a bit burdensome, to have
写出一个构造函数，构造一个这样的状态。
to write out a constructor and
construct a state like this.
也就是， TypeScript 不能弄明白，对吧 ?
It also is,
TypeScript can't figure this out, right?
这样做的更好方式是我想让你动作快点
And so there's a better way of doing
this that I wanna show you really quick,
以实例化您的状态。
to instantiate your state.
如果您控制了 Bobel 配置，那么可以执行此操作。
If you have control of your Babel config,
then you can do this.
如果不是的话，你可能不会，所以超级
If not, then you may not,
so it would be super
如果我们只能执行状态 = ，那么有用。
useful if we could just do
state = .
> > Brian Holt: 如果你能那样做，那岂不是更棒吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Wouldn't that be a lot
nicer, if you could just do it that way?
其实你可以的
Well, you actually can.
但事实是这实际上是
But the thing is that this
is actually a proposal for
一个 JavaScript，它其实还不是一个真正的东西，但是你可以让它工作。
a JavaScript, and it's not actually a real
thing quite yet, but you can make it work.
所以这会用 JavaScript来降落
So this will land in JavaScript,
我认为它实际上是在 2019 年或 2020年着陆。
I think it's actually going
to land in 2019 or 2020.
所以我要给你们展示如何修改你的巴贝尔配置 ( 如果你必须的话 ) 。
So I'm gonna show you how to modify your
Babel config, if you have to, with React.
所以我需要你做的第一件事就是在这里打开你的指挥线路。
So the first thing I need you to
do is open your command line here.
>> Brian Holt: 你可以在这里看到，支持
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
you can see here it says, Support for
当前未启用实验语法 "classProperties" 。
the experimental syntax 'classProperties'
isn't currently enabled.
然后我们就能动作快点了
And we're just gonna go
enable that really quick.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我希望您执行 npm 安装 -D，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I want you to do npm install -D, and
你要安装一些东西来做这个工作。
you have to install quite a few
things to make this work.
babel-eslint @babel/core @babel/preset-env
@babel/plugin-plug-in-class-properties。
@babel/plugin-proposal-class-properties.
我不知道这些我很抱歉
I don't name these, I'm very sorry.
@babel/ 预设置反应。
And @babel/preset-react.
>> Brian Holt: 你现在都在打字吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You're all
done typing that now?
我只是开个玩笑这很有需要
I'm just kidding, it's a lot to type.
>> Brian Holt: 那么这里发生了什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what's going on here?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 这些东西都建在包裹里
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All this
stuff is built into Parcel,
而派塞尔一直在为我们处理这个问题
and Parcel has just been handling this for
us.
但是，它给了我们一个逃跑的舱门，如果我们有定制的需求，
However, it gives us the escape
hatch that if we have custom needs,
在这件案子里我们是因为没有这个
which in this case we do because
it doesn't have this one,
@babel/plugin-pl建议书-class-properties
the
@babel/plugin-proposal-class-properties
我们可以说，嘿包裹，用我们的配置，而不是你的配置。
,that we can say, hey Parcel,
use our config instead of your config.
他们的配置是基本的，让我们以现代的 JavaScript为目标，
Their config is basically like,
let's target modern JavaScript,
基本上，已经用有效的 JavaScript 提供的所有内容。
basically, everything that has
already shipped with valid JavaScript.
一般来说我不会说船要做实验用的 JavaScript
In general, I don't say ship to
production experimental JavaScript,
除了我没问题因为这个肯定会降落的
except I'm okay with this one because
this one's definitely gonna land.
事实上我相信它已经降落了如果我记错的话
In fact, I believe it has already landed,
and if I remember reading correctly,
上周它降落了
last week it landed.
>> Brian Holt: 但总的来说，这会咬你的屁股。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But in general,
that can bite you in the butt.
所以我们会安装这个
So we'll install that.
>> Brian Holt: 需要花费第二个时间来完成所有这些内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It should take a second
to go through and load all that stuff.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍特( Brian Holt) : 我想，当这一过程完成时，它就完成了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I guess while this
is finishing, there, it finished.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我希望您在此处创建新文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I want you to create a new file here.
我想让你把它叫做点，而不是在源头里面，在收养我的里面，
And I want you to call it dot,
not inside the source, inside of adopt me,
项目的根目录。
the root directory the project.
给它打电话巴伯 rc
Call it .babelrc.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，使用了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, yes, used on.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，在这里，我想让你把预置
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, inside of here
I want you to put presets, and
然后我们就把两个东西放在预集里
then we're gonna put two
things here in presets.
其中之一是 @babel/preset 反应。
One of them's gonna be,
@babel/preset-react.
其中一个是 @babel/preset-env。
And one of these is gonna
be @babel/preset-env.
>> Brian Holt: 根据我们的信息，我们将放置插件，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Under that
we're gonna put plugins, and
在此我们将放置 @babel/plugin-plug-in -class-properties。
inside of that we'll put
@babel/plugin-proposal-class-properties.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 让我们来谈谈这两件事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's talk
about what those two things are.
巴贝反应会带来所有你需要的东西
presets babel react is brings with
it all the things that you need to
错位的雷法对吧
transpile React, right?
因此，在理解 JSX 时，它也会带来流量。
So in understanding JSX,
it also brings Flow.
不是我们正在使用流，而是包含在针对 React的预置中。
Not that we're using Flow at all, but
that is included in the preset for React.
这就是 JSX周围的一系列的情况。
It's a bunch of transpilations around JSX.
@babel/preset-env，这是
@babel/preset-env, this is
一个漂亮的，我应该提一下，一个预设就是一组插件，对吧 ?
a pretty, and I should mention that,
a preset is a group of plugins, right?
所以在这件案子里我们要带来一个转变
So in this case we're bringing
one transformation, but
我们预设的是一堆插件，就是一堆转换。
our preset is a bunch of plugins,
which is a bunch of transformations.
这将为您指定的环境转码。
This will transpile your code for
the environment that you specify.
幸运的是你和我已经指定了一个环境
So luckily, you and I have already
specified an environment, and
就在我们的包里
that is in our package.json.
还记得我们什么时候做的吗
Remember when we did this?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这个预置-env 将会查看此浏览器列表，并表示凉爽。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this preset-env is gonna
look at this browsers list, and say, cool.
我要把所有的 JavaScript 都转了这样就能在这些浏览器里工作了
I'm gonna transpile all the JavaScript so
it works in these browsers.
>> Brian Holt: 这样做不会有太多的原因，因为 JavaScript 的 cuz 工作在
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So that won't be very many
things because, cuz of JavaScript works in
这些浏览器是因为这些都是非常新的浏览器，好吗 ?
these browsers because these
are very very new browsers, okay?
> > Brian Holt: 但你还能做些很酷的事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
there's pretty cool stuff you can do.
实际上，您可以将 Google Analytics 导入到预先设置的环境中，并且
You can actually import your
Google Analytics into preset-env, and
它会特别为你的用户而转，对吧 ?
it will actually transpile it
specifically for your users, right?
你可以说，嘿，这是我的谷歌分析。
So you can say, hey,
here's my Google Analytics.
移植它，使 99% 的人可以看到我的网站。
Transpile it so that 99% of
these people can see my website.
>> Brian Holt: 已构建到浏览器列表包中。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That's built
into the browserlist package.
我们今天不会这么做但这是有可能的
We're not gonna do that today,
but it is possible.
好的，然后这里的插件，这才是真正允许的
Okay, and then the plugins here,
this is what's actually going to allow
我们要做的就是我刚刚给你看的那个语法好吗
us to do that syntax that
I just showed you, okay?
我需要你再做一件事
I need you to do one more thing here.
所以把这个给你的 .babelrc
So save this to your .babelrc.
我需要您打开 .eslintrc 文件，并且我们必须添加解析器选项。
I need you to open you .eslintrc file,
and we have to add a parser option.
所以我需要你帮我把你的孩子给我
So parser, and
I need you to put babel-eslint.
所以在这一点上
So up to this point,
埃斯特林特已经能够理解我们一直使用的所有代码
eslint has been able to understand
all the code that we have been using.
但现在我们又增加了一个新的实验特征
But now we've added a new experimental
feature that eslint would choke on,
所以我们得说用巴贝尔来理解这个代码
so we have to say,
use Babel to understand this code.
这都是这么做的
And that's all this does.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特( Brian Holt) : 现在，这似乎是一种使用一个功能的礼节，但
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, this might seem like
a lot of ritual to use one feature, but
我通常不会只为一个这样的功能而去做。
I typically wouldn't do it just for
one feature like this.
但这对如何使用 Babel 有更多的指导意义
But this is actually to be more
instructive on how to use Babel and
包裹在一起
Parcel together.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，现在你把 17 线放在那里，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now that you've put in that line 17 there,
我们回到我们的 " SearchParams " 页面
let's go back to our SearchParams page.
现在，不是 SearchParams，而是详细信息。
And now, not SearchParams,
we were on Details rather.
现在这样挺好的
Now it's fine with this.
>> Brian Holt: 很酷，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Pretty cool, right?
> > Brian Holt: 现在，如果我没有错的话，你应该可以说。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, if I'm not mistaken,
you should be able to say this.state.,
然后就知道你在上面装货了
and then it knows that you
have loading on there.
这是因为现在 TypeScript 可以理解您的组件，对吗 ?
That's because now TypeScript can
understand your component, right?
它不知道你有媒体，有繁殖，有负荷量，
Notice it doesn't actually know that you
have media, and breed, and load, and
有些其他的因为我们在这里没有把它实例化
some of these other ones,
because we didn't instantiate it up here.
但是 TypeScript 现在有能力去运行代码和理解，好的，
But TypeScript has the ability now to go
and run on your code and understand, okay,
你有这些东西在你的组件上
you have these things on your component.
我可以给你自动完成这些东西
I can autocomplete these things for you.
所以如果我想在这里设定名字就像这样
So if I want in here and
set name: blink like that, just set and
实例化为某种缺省情况。
instantiate to be some
sort of default thing.
这就意味着我可以来这儿说
That means I can come down here and
say, this.state., and
那么现在通知名字也在这里
then notice now a name is in here as well.
>> Brian Holt: 这是 TypeScript 的魔力，以及针对该问题的 VS 代码。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's the magic of
TypeScript, and VS Code for that matter.
> > Brian Holt: 我们稍后会了解到的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We'll get to that later,
though.
有一段关于 TypeScript 的部分，因此。
There's a whole section on TypeScript, so.
>> Brian Holt: 如果不起作用呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What if it doesn't work?
我开玩笑的 让我们看看这里发生了什么
I'm just kidding.
[LAUGH] Let's see what happened here.
>> Brian Holt: 此 .state.returt ，是否在某处保留了 this.state ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This .state.return,
did I leave a this.state in somewhere?
是啊太奇怪了
Yeah, that's weird.
>> Brian Holt: 有了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There it goes.
那只是给我看这个名字之类的
That was just for
me showing this.name and stuff like that,
比把它裹在那条线上
prettier than just wrap it onto that line.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 酷，好，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Cool, so yeah,
现在还在和公共阶层的财产合作
now that's still working with
the public class property.
这就是所谓的。
It's actually what that's called.